Anything that is harmful to you or to society, anything that is dangerous to you or to civil order, Allah has made it haram.
Therefore, I'm telling you from now, you're not gonna understand every single ruling of Islam.
You're not. Because that's not the purpose. There will be rulings you might be confused by.
What is the wisdom? So find out, is it an act of...
So never, ever give up hope in a lie.
If you fell down, you have to stand up and continue walking.
If you got yourself dirty, take a shower, change your clothes, and I mean physically and spiritually.
Because we don't want to see you happy.
No, we are strict because we want to see you happy.
We are strict because we want to see you succeed.
Dear youngsters, a day will come when you are parents
that you will realize how much we love you.
At this stage, it's too much for you to understand.
But all that we do is out of love, out of concern, out of care.
Every parent knows to see you succeed is our success.
We will gladly give up our happiness for your happiness.
and in that trying will be your success and our success as well. May Allah SWT bless me and you
withran through the Qur'an and may He make us of those who its verses they understand and
apply its halal and haram throughout our lifespan. I ask Allah's forgiveness, you as well ask Him
For He is the wafoor and the rahmah.
Al-Habdullillah, all praise is due to Allah, the One and the Unique.
He is who we worship, and it is His aid that we seek.
he is the lord of the oppressed and he hears the prayer of the weak. As to what follows,
How cruel the world can be and maybe I'm not qualified to try to explain